{
	"Questions" : {
		"1" : {
			"question" : "The return keyword used to transfer control from a function back to the calling function.",
			"option1" : "Yes",
			"option2" : "Switch",
			"option3" : "go back",
			"option4" : "goto",
			"answer" : "Yes"
		},
		"2" : {
			"question" : "How do you specify double constant 3.14 as a long double?",
			"option1" : "By using LD after 3.14",
			"option2" : "By using L after 3.14",
			"option3" : "By using DL after 3.14",
			"option4" : "By using LF after 3.14",
			"answer" : "By using L after 3.14"
		},
		"3" : {
			"question" : "Similarity between a structure, union and enumeration",
			"option1" : "All are helpful in defining new variables",
			"option2" : "All are helpful in defining new pointers",
			"option3" : "All are helpful in defining new data types",
			"option4" : "All are helpful in defining new structures",
			"answer" : "All are helpful in defining new data types"
		},
		"4" : {
			"question" : "Identify the C compiler of UNIX.",
			"option1" : "gcc",
			"option2" : "cc",
			"option3" : "Borland",
			"option4" : "vc++",
			"answer" : "cc"
		},
		"5" : {
			"question" : "To print a double value which format specifier can be used?",
			"option1" : "%L",
			"option2" : "%If",
			"option3" : "%Lf",
			"option4" : "None of the above",
			"answer" : "%If"
		},
		"6" : {
			"question" : "The library function strrchr() finds the first occurrence of a substring in another string.",
			"option1" : "Yes",
			"option2" : "Strstr()",
			"option3" : "strchr()",
			"option4" : "strnset()",
			"answer" : "Strstr()"
		},
		"7" : {
			"question" : "In C, parameters are always",
			"option1" : "Passed by value",
			"option2" : "Passed by reference",
			"option3" : "Non-pointer variables are passed by value",
			"option4" : "Passed by value result",
			"answer" : "Passed by value"
		},
		"8" : {
			"question" : "Which of the following is true about return type of functions in C?",
			"option1" : "Functions can return any type",
			"option2" : "Functions can return any type except array and functions",
			"option3" : "Functions can return any type except functions and union",
			"option4" : "Functions can return any type except array and union",
			"answer" : "Functions can return any type except array and functions"
		},
		"9" : {
			"question" : "Which of the following true about FILE *fp",
			"option1" : "FILE is a keyword in C",
			"option2" : "FILE is a structure",
			"option3" : "FILE is a stream",
			"option4" : "FILE is a buffered stream",
			"answer" : "FILE is a structure"
		},
		"10" : {
			"question" : "When fopen() is not able to open a file, it returns",
			"option1" : "EOF",
			"option2" : "NULL",
			"option3" : "Runtime Error",
			"option4" : "Compiler Dependent",
			"answer" : "NULL"
		}
	}
}